Guide to the Yale University Building Project Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University building project records
1891-2007
RU 5
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
472.75
(246 boxes)
The records consist of proposals, specifications, correspondence, memoranda, reports, schedules, drawings, a 16mm film, and administrative records, maintained by the Yale Office of Facilities, documenting construction and renovation projects for Yale buildings. Also included is detailed information about the design and installation of mechanical, laboratory, and other equipment and systems.
Yale University. Office of Facilities
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of Facilities, 1989-2008. Accession 2012-A-075 received in 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of proposals, specifications, correspondence, memoranda, reports, schedules, drawings, a 16mm film, and administrative records, maintained by the Yale Office of Facilities, documenting construction and renovation projects for Yale buildings. Also included is detailed information about the design and installation of mechanical, laboratory, and other equipment and systems.
Arrangement
The records are arranged as follows: I. Specifications, correspondence, and other project records, 1891-1985. II. Drawings, 1912-1988; and subsequent accessions.
Campus planning; College buildings -- Design and construction; Architectural drawings (visual works); Architectural records; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Office of Facilities
- Specifications, correspondence, and other project records, 1891-1985; Series I
  Arrangement
  Arranged by region/chronology (building) number.
  Scope and Contents
  Building specifications, cost lists, charts, reports, correspondence, memoranda, proposals, smaller drawings, and the like, from 1891 to 1985, comprise this large collection of documentation from the erstwhile Architectural and Engineering Services (now Facilities Planning). The materials address aspects of overall building construction and renovation, as well as detailed work in plumbing, ventilation, heating, air-conditioning, and electrical fixtures. The purchase, installation, and maintenance of building equipment (especially in university dining halls and science or medical laboratories) is also documented.
  Please note that most drawings originally found in these files were removed for proper storage and preservation. These drawings are inventoried in Series II.
  Conditions Governing Access
  In accordance with university policy, the records are restricted until January 1, 2021.
  - 1 Old Campus
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Lighting alterations, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1:02 Connecticut Hall
    - Carpentry, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Masonry, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Plumbing and heating, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Restoration, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Mechanical files, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Restoration, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Lighting for study hall, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alterations (heating), 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Fire escape specifications, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1:17 Dwight Hall
    - Electrical, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Plumbing, heating, and ventilation, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1:20 Street Hall
    - Architect's notes and specifications for additions, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - General specifications for alterations, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Renovation - electrical work, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alteration - architectural, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Ventilation, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 1:23 Farnam Hall
    - Carpentry, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1911-1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Plumbing, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Masonry, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Steel and iron work, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - 1:23, 1:29 Farnam and Lawrance Halls
    - Modernization, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1:23, 1:29, 1:32 Farnam, Lawrance, and Welch Halls
    - General specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Hardware specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Painting specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Plumbing fixture specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Telephone specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Toilet accessory specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Vault door specifications, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - 1:24 Durfee Hall
    - General and miscellaneous, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Carpentry, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Electrical, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Plumbing, heating, and ventilation, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Renovations, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Revisions to renovations specifications, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1:25 Battell Chapel
    - General, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - 1:29 Lawrance Hall
    - Alterations, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Electrical work, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - 1:30, 1:39 Linsly and Chittenden Halls
    - Alterations, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Room 101 - projection booth, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Old Campus feeder extension to Sterling Memorial Library, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1:32 Welch Hall
    - Plumbing/heating specifications, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Campus Police alterations, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Lighting, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - 1:33 Vanderbilt Hall
    - General specifications, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - 1:35 Phelps Hall
    - Equipment specifications, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Dedications, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Millwork, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Electrical equipment submitted: fire alarms, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Electrical fixtures, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Fire escape/stairs, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Heating/plumbing approved, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Library furniture, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Mechanical specifications, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Metal shelving, doors, frames, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Alterations, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 59-60)
    - Approved hardware and hardware schedule, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Furniture: library, lounge, information office, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Heating, ventilation, air-conditioning, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Payne elevator, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Electrical alterations, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Electronic Security and Control Systems, Inc.: Campus Police computer, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1:39 Linsly Hall
    - Roof repair specifications, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - 1:40 Wright Hall
    - Electrical specifications, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Heating and ventilation specifications, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - General specifications, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Hardware specifications, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Tile and marble specifications, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Contractor's proposal, 1912? (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Plumbing specifications, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Elevator specifications, 1931 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Filter system, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Basement renovation (post office), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - 1:43 McClellan Hall
    - Carpentry work, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Electrical work, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Masonry work, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Painting and glazing, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Plumbing and heating, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Steel and iron work, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - 1:44 Bingham Hall
    - General, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 85-86)
    - Carpentry, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Electrical, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Heating, ventilation, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Painting and glazing, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Plumbing, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - General, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - M.B. Foster Electric Company: shop drawings, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Bingham-Durfee study, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - 2:04 27 High St.
    - Estimates, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - 2:11 Yale Hope Mission
    - Specifications, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - 2:12 295-297 Crown St.
    - Alterations, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - 2:15 Yale University Press
    - Steel framing, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Alterations, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - 2:29 Yale Repertory Theatre
    - Lighting renovation, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - 2:33 (Mellon) British Art Center
    - Electrical, fire sprinklers, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Log and transmittal file, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Specifications, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 103-104)
    - Lighting specifications, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - HVAC system adjustment, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 106-108)
    - Electrical work, undated (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - 3 98 Park St.
    - Basement lighting, no date (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - 3:07 University Theatre
    - Library addition, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Specifications, 1926 (Box 3, Folder 112-113)
    - Specifications, 1954-1967 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - 3:09 294-296 Elm St.
    - Specifications, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - 3:25 Pierson and Davenport Colleges
    - Inventory, correspondence, plans, 1927-1934 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Tunnel construction, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Elevator and dumbwaiter specifications, 1930-1931 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Carpentry, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Plumbing, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Heating, ventilation, refrigeration, 1930-1932 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Electrical work specifications, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Steel and iron work, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Painting and glazing specifications, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Electrical, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Lighting alterations (Pierson), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - 3:26 Briton Hadden Memorial
    - Miscellaneous, 1931 (Box 3, Folder 129-130)
  - 3:31 215 Park St.
    - Alteration drawings, undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Political Union expansion, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - 3:32 Beta Theta Pi Fraternity House, 204 York St.
    - Specifications, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Alterations, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - 3:33 205 Park St.
    - Specifications, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - 3:34 306 Elm St.
    - Alterations, 1934 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - 3:37 215 Park St.
    - Specifications, 1930 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - 3:42 Chi Psi Fraternity House, 211 Park St.
    - Specifications, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - 3:43 Art and Architecture Building
    - Specifications, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Electrical specifications, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Structural specifications, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Log and transmittal file, 1962-1971 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Renovations, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Rehabilitations, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Renovations, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Renovations, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - 3:63 Fence Club (Psi Upsilon Fraternity House)
    - Specifications, 1928? (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - 4:18 149 Elm St. (Faculty Club)
    - Alterations, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - 4:22 232 York St. (Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity House)
    - Various specifications, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - 4:24 Miller Property
    - Specifications and notes, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Weir Hall specifications, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - 4:28 Branford and Saybrook Colleges
    - Electrical fixtures, 1921-1922 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Plumbing, heating, ventilation, refrigeration, 1930-1933 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Carpentry, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Electrical, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - General, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 156-157)
    - Masonry, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Specifications for structural steel work, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Elevators, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Specifications for steel and iron work, 1932-1933 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Specifications for steel and iron work (Harkness Tower), 1932-1934 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Fan motors, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Carpentry, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Re-used fixtures, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Masonry, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Painting and glazing, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Specifications (Branford College), 1933 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Electrical, 1933-1934 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Electrical valves, 1934-1935 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Basement renovation (Branford College), 1933 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Air-conditioning: Branford College Master"s office, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Saybrook College dining hall, undated (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Electrical work for basement (Saybrook College), undated (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - 4:34 Jonathan Edwards College
    - Painting and glazing, 1924, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Masonry, 1924-1925, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Steel and iron work, 1924-1925, 1931-1932 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Tunnel, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Light and ornamental work, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Electrical work, 1925-32 (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Plumbing, heating, ventilation, refrigeration, 1925, 1931-1933 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Plumbing, heating, ventilation, refrigeration, 1931-1933 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Alterations, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Carpentry, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Elevators and dumbwaiters, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Lighting, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1932-1933 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Valve chart, 1933 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Kitchen equipment list, letters, 1933-1934 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Renovations, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Dumbwaiter wiring diagrams, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - 4:37 Yale University Art Gallery
    - Electrical, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Elevators, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Specifications for heating and ventilation, 1926 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Ventilation, lighting, mechanical, 1926-1953 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Electrical, 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - General, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Plan index, 1927 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Carpentry, 1927-1928 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - General, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - General, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Plumbing and draining, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Design laboratory construction, 195 (Box 6, Folder 204)
    - Design laboratory heating and ventilation, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 205)
    - Design laboratory electrical specifications, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 206)
    - Design laboratory plumbing specifications, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 207)
    - Design laboratory electrical equipment, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Design laboratory fans, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Air-conditioning for offices, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 210)
    - Design laboratory air systems, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Photography room, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Renovations, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 213)
    - Electrical systems, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 214)
    - Addition, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 215)
    - Electrical and telephone maintenance, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 216)
    - Lighting control center, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Information for bidders for the "Mabel Brady Garven Galleries Exhibit Display", undated (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Plumbing, undated (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Calculations, undated (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Design laboratory plumbing fixtures, undated (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - 5:07 Yale Co-op
    - General specifications #14, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - 5:10 Hall of Graduate Studies
    - Carpentry, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Elevators and dumbwaiters, 1930 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Electrical work, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Masonry, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Painting and glazing, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Specifications, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Miscellaneous specifications, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Plumbing, heating, ventilation, refrigeration, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Steel and iron work, 1931-1932 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - Kitchen equipment, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 232-233)
    - Room directories, 1932 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Air-conditioning, basement alteration, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Dining hall: alterations and specifications, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Room alterations, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - 5:16, 5:17 Morse and Ezra Stiles Colleges
    - Fire pumps, 1948-1960 (Box 7, Folder 238)
    - General Electric identification specifications, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 239)
    - Plumbing, heating, air-conditioning manuals, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 240)
    - Hardware, 1959-1962 (Box 7, Folder 241)
    - Ceiling tile, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 242)
    - Ceramic accessories, Masters= houses, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 243)
    - Construction sign, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 244)
    - Stores building, finish schedules, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 245)
    - Electrical fixtures, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 246)
    - Pumps: miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 247)
    - Roofing and flashing, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 248)
    - Electrical - switchgear panels, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 249)
    - Sidewalk hatchway at 65 Broadway, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 250)
    - Bubbletrol for sewage pumps, Doutrol for booster pumps W1-E4, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 251)
    - Machinery/standard specifications, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 252)
    - Specifications for new colleges, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 253-254)
    - Specifications notes, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 255)
    - Elevator cars and doors, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 256)
    - Fans: roof, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 257)
    - Hardware schedules, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 258)
    - Heating, ventilation, 1960-19617 (Box 7, Folder 259-260)
    - Plumbing specifications, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 261)
    - Slate, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 262)
    - Refrigerator doors, miscellaneous, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 263)
    - Plumbing Approved, 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 264)
    - Kitchen Equipment, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Plumbing, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Buttery, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Dining Hall Roof Truss, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Elevators, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Hardware Schedule, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Heating and Ventilating Approved, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Hodges Asam: Photographs, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Installation/Maintenance Tags for Pump, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Kitchen Appliances, Master"s Houses, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Kitchenettes, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Snow-Melting Cores and Anti-Freeze, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Revision to Roof Parapet Flashing, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Rooms: Singles, Doubles, Fellow"s Apartments, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Temperature Controls, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 279-280)
    - Miscellaneous Electrical, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Television, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Electrical, Fire Alarms, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Report on Deteriorating Effects of Modern Light Sources, circa 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Underground Pipe Insulation, 1961-1969 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Automatic Transfer Switch Catalog 905206-905224C, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Change Orders, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 287-288)
    - Pre-Cast Architectural Concrete, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - General Electrical Apparatus/Maintenance, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 290)
    - Electrical Extras, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 291)
    - Electrical Switches, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 292)
    - Field Memorandum, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 293)
    - Edwards Electric Fire Alarm, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 294)
    - Furniture, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 295)
    - Inspections and Checklists, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 296)
    - Landscaping, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 297)
    - Miscellaneous Metalwork, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 298)
    - Before Final Payment, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 299)
    - Punch List, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 300)
    - Real Estate: 69 Broadway, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 301)
    - Snack Bar, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - Stage Lighting, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 303)
    - Letters, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - General Correspondence (Ezra Stiles College), 1962-1970 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Checklists, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Electrical Heating, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Kitchen Costs, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Kitchen Vent, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 309)
    - Storm Windows, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 310)
    - "To Do", 1963 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Buttery (Morse College), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Purchase Orders, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Specifications, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Walkway Lighting, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Concrete and Rubble, undated (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Change Orders, undated (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Co-op Building (H, P, V), undated (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Steel Door Frames, undated (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Subcontractors, undated (Box 8, Folder 320)
    - Automatic Temperature Control, undated (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - 5:18 Yale Co-op
    - Budget, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Trans. Vault, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Electrical, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - Miscellaneous Electric Plans and Schedules, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Heating, Ventilation, and Air-Conditioning, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - Miscellaneous Metalwork, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 327)
    - Plumbing, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 328)
    - Ventilation, Hardware, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 329)
    - Maintenance of Air-Conditioning System, 1962, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - Letters, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - Elevators, undated (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - Automatic Temperature Control for Yale Co-op (W-6), Morse, and Ezra Stiles Colleges, undated (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - Temperature Control, undated (Box 9, Folder 334)
  - 6 York Square Tunnels, 1927-1929 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - 6:04 Central Power Plant
    - Instruction Manuals, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 336)
    - Chilled Water System, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 337-344)
  - 6:05 Service Bureaus (20 Ashmun St.)
    - Addition, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - Addition, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Alterations, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Renovations of Loading Dock, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - 6:12 106 York St.
    - Alterations, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - 6:16 Payne Whitney Gymnasium
    - Tunnels, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Plumbing, Heating, Ventilation, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 351-352)
    - Steel and Ironwork, 1930-1931 (Box 9, Folder 353)
    - Masonry Work, 1930-1932 (Box 9, Folder 354)
    - Painting and Glazing, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 355)
    - Plumbing Pumps, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 356)
    - Carpentry, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Rowing Tanks, 1931-1932 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Electrical Work, 1931-1933 (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Specifications, 1931-1945 (Box 10, Folder 360-361)
    - Elevators, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Motor Brush, 1932 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Rowing Tanks, 1932-1939 (Box 10, Folder 364)